Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 5. Accessions 2006-207 and 2007-081, 54.75 Linear feet
  - Subseries 3. Negatives
    - Beckman (8 folders), 1989-1993 (Box-folder 29-9, Box-folder 30-7)
      Negatives: rolls: 1-11, 13, 14, 16, 17, note attached c. 1993: "12 and 15 used for ACT News, intern. Public"; Rolls 15214, 15217, 19342, 19336, 21244, 21559-21563, 21565-21568, 23889, 23891, 29112, "Beckman A-E" (color), 8001-8016, 8266-8280, 8285-8288, 8448-8464, 8465-8471, 8750-8759, 8792-8796, 8813-8816, 8833, 8834, 9408, 9409, 9412, 63627-63633, 76784-76797.
      Note: There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 15214, 15217, 19342, 23889, 23891, 29112, "Beckman A-E" (color), 8001-8016, 8266-8280, 8285-8288, 8448-8464, 8750-8759, 8792-8796, 8813-8816. There are no negatives for rolls 19270.
    - Charles Schwab, binder 1, 1996 (Flat-box 30, Folders 8-14)
      Negatives: rolls: 1733-11791.
    - Charles Schwab, binder 2 ( 3 folders), 1996 (Box-folder 30-15, Box-folder 31-2)
      Negatives: rolls: 1227-2357, 1262-1290.
    - CKS MCI, 1995 (Flat-box 31, Folders 3-6)
      Negatives: rolls: 01777-01781, 75549-75576.
    - Clement Mok, 1990 (Flat-box 31, Folders 7-9)
      Negatives: rolls: 8522-8533, 8546-8550, 8725, 8728, 8923-8933.
    - Clement Mok, 1991 (Flat-box 31, Folders 10-14)
      Negatives: rolls: 9176-9177, 9185, 9292-9297, 74153-74157, 74159-74186.
    - Clement Mok, 1995 (Flat-box 31, Folders 15-19)
      Negatives: rolls: 72955-72960, 72965, 78593, 49390-49402, 78593, 97076, 97086-97098, 6401-6419.
      Note: 6418 and 6419 are stored in same plastic sleeve.
    - Clon Tech (5 folders), 1996 (Box-folder 31-20, Box-folder 32-4)
      Negatives: rolls: 79020-79039, 0187-01508.
    - CMC, 1993 (Flat-box 32, Folder 5)
      Negatives: rolls: 6487-64494, 70676.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 93-99, 16, 20, 29-39.
    - Coblentz, 1992 (Flat-box 32, Folders 6-14)
      Negatives: rolls: 88484-88525, 0046-0055.
    - Coblentz, 1994 (Flat-box 32, Folder 15)
      Negatives: rolls: 91691-91703.
    - Coblentz Identity Brochure, 1998 (Flat-box 32, Folder 16)
      Negatives: rolls: 41090-41093, 41095-41101.
    - Credit Suisse, 1999 (Flat-box 32, Folders 17-20)
      Negatives: rolls: 69474-69487, 6945-69473.
    - Diefenbach, binder 2, 1991 (Flat-box 33, Folders 1-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 9188-9196, 72004-72019, 72021-72023.
    - Dupont, 1991 (Flat-box 33, Folders 4-9)
      Negatives: rolls: 66870-66885, 66894-66904, 66961-66964, 66966-66971, 67001.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 66965.
    - EG&G, 1996 (Flat-box 33, Folders 10-14)
      Negatives: rolls: 10367-10400, 10402-10404.
    - Evolve/Cortez (4 folders), 1995-1996 (Box-folder 33-15, Box-folder 34-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 00415, 66749-66752, 01624, 01360-01368, 01742, 02031-02034, 03218-03222, 71473, 71116-71122, 00234, 73916, 02968, 02975, 74814-74816, 00391, 06828, 06829, 06654-06658, 07839-07841, 00401-00405, 00464, 0939-09356, 10020-10024, 01797-01802, 01874, 01875, 01921-01924, 10428, 12049, 12051.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 752, 922.
    - Farallon, 1989 January - November (Flat-box 53, Folders 1-6)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 27137, 16150-16152, 16154-16156, 17661-17666, 19709, 19710, 22063-22066, 22133-22136, 22850, 22959, 22961, 22963, 22964, 23915-23918, 31515-31523, 31525, 31526, 31528.
    - Farallon, 1990 January - June (Flat-box 53, Folders 7-11)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 8252-8257, 8290, 8292-8296, 8298, 8299, 8323, 8324, 8327, 8328, 04218, 04095, 04096, B-03932-B-03934, B-03937, B-03940, A-97925, A-98384, 8434-8438, 8492, 8484, 8572, 8703. Note: contains tech edit sheet
    - Farallon, 1989 December (Flat-box 53, Folders 12-13)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 8066-8069, 8072, 8119, 8120, 8123-8127, 8130, 8166-8172.
    - Farallon, 1990 July - December (Flat-box 53, Folders 14-18)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 8573-8575, 8605, 8701, 8704, 8705, 8706, 8710, 8711, 8763, 8767-8769, 8773-8775, 8777-8780, 8789, 8822-8826, 8831, 8832, 63575-63584, 63620-63626.
    - Farallon, 1991-1992 (Flat-box 53, Folders 19-20)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 9146-9153, 9161-9166, 9186, 9187, 74468.
    - Farallon C (Flat-box 55, Folders 9-11)
      Black and white negatives: rolls: 27843, A-97924, 26611, 26616, 26617, 27058, 29468, 29463, 29470, 29472, 63574, A-98383, 28772, 27853, 31524, 31521, 74469-74471, A, A-97926, A-98382.
    - FTF, 1996 (Flat-box 35, Folders 4-6)
      Negatives: rolls: 24592-24597, 12541-12551, 30498-30502, 41188-41191.
    - Gain Technology, 1992 (Flat-box 34, Folders 4-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 0016-0029.
    - Granite, 1995 (Flat-box 34, Folders 6-12)
      Negatives: rolls: 09517-09523, 09525-09544, 09609-09613, 09626-09645, 09651.
      Note: roll 09528 is incomplete, negatives 19-30 are missing; note attached: "sent to Portfolio ’97 selects."
    - Howe-Lewis, 1994 (Flat-box 34, Folders 13-19)
      Negatives: rolls: 76390-76429, 78410, 78417-78423, 78438-78444, 79069-79076.
    - HP Labs (4 folders), 1995 (Box-folder 34-20, Box-folder 35-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 05524-05549, 05620-05627.
    - IBM, Burlington, 1997 December (Flat-box 55, Folders 6-8)
      Negatives: rolls: 60-91.
    - IBM, Executive Arts, 1997 November (Flat-box 55, Folders 3-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 1-12, 14-32.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls: 1, frames 31-36; 2, frames 6-11; 5, frames 5-16; 6, frames 6-11, 18-36; 7, frames 1-11, 18-23; 8, frames 6-17, 24-29; 9, frames 1-12, 19-24; 11, frames 13-18, 31-36; 12, frames 1-6, 19-24; 14, frames 6-17, 24-34; 15, frames 7-24; 17, frames 12-17, 24-29; 18, frames 6-11, 24-29; 19, frames 31-36; 20, frames 6-11; 21, frames 6-17; 22, frames 25-30; 23, frames 1-4, 23-34; 24, frames 7-12, 19-30; 26, frames 1-6; 29, frames 19-30; 31, frames 7-12; 32, frames 25-30. There are no negatives for the following roll: 13.
    - IBM, Fishkill, 1997 November (Flat-box 55, Folders 1-2)
      Negatives: rolls: 37-59.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls: 37, frames 13-18; 38, frames 1-6; 41, frames 19-24; 42, frames 1-12; 43, frames 13-18; 44, frames 1-6, 13-18, 31-36; 47, frames 19-24.
    - IBM, New York, Executive Arts, 1997 November (Flat-box 49, Folders 17-20)
      Negatives: rolls 1-36.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls: 1, frames 6-11; 2, frames 25-30; 6, frames 19-24, 7-12; 9, frames 7-12; 10, frames 1-6, 25-30; 11, frames 1-12, 19-24; 14, frames 8-23, 30-35; 15, frames 1-6, 31-36; 17, frames 25-30, 24, frames 25-30; 25, frames 1-6, 19-24; 26, frames 1-24; 27, frames 7-12, 31-36; 28, frames 31-36; 31, frames 6-11, 30-35; 32, frames 13-30; 34, frames 7-24; 35, frames 19-30; 36, frames 19-24.
    - Instinet Hong Kong, 1994 (Flat-box 35, Folders 7-11)
      Negatives: rolls: 88648-88683, 88877-88879. 88684-8868.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled /"CD makeup": 88654, frames 13-18; 88558, frames 18-24; 55660, frames 18-33; 88662, frames 1-6, 13-25; 88663, frames 7-12; 88688, frames 13-18; 88670, frames 31-36; 88667, frames 20-25; 88672, frames 31, 32, 35, 36; 88673, frames 1-5, 25-30; 88678, frames 25-30, 88680, frames 19-24; 88681, frames 19-24; 88682, frames 13-24; 88683, frames 7-12, 25-30; 88877, frames 13-18, 25-34; 88879, frames 1-6; 88684, frames 1-12, 25-30; 88685, frames 7-12; 88686, frames 19-23; 88687, frames 31-36.
    - Instinet, binder 1, 1994 (Flat-box 35, Folders 12-15)
      Negatives: rolls: 33386-33413, 30523-30527, 1702.
      Note: The following negatives are missing from their respective rolls, labeled “CD makeup”: 33389, frames 13-18; 33391, frames 18-30; 33396, frames 31-36; 33400, frames 7-12; 33403, frames 19-24; 33405, frames 7-12, 19-24, 31-36; 33406, frames 13-18; 33411, frames 25-30; 33400, frames 7-12; 33403, frames 19-24; 33405, frames 7-12, 19-24, 31-36.
    - Instinet, binder 2 (4 folders), 1994 (Box-folder 35-16, Box-folder 36-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 88380-88407, 88463 88474, 88477-88484, 88489, 88639, 1234, 1702, 1703, 88629-88635.
    - Kaleida, 1992 (Flat-box 36, Folders 4-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 81311-81320, 88448-88456.
    - Kodak Developers Conference, 1992 (Flat-box 36, Folders 6-13)
      Negatives: rolls: K1, K2, K4, K5, K7-K15, K17-K24, K26, K28-K31, K33-K69, K71-K73, K75-K84, 190.
    - Kodak, binder 1, 1991 (Flat-box 36, Folders 14-17)
      Negatives: rolls: 10003, 10004, 68159-68179, 68181-69185.
    - Kodak, binder 2, 1991 (Flat-box 37, Folders 1-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 68195-68220, 68222-68224.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 68221.
    - LEK/Alcar, 1993 (Flat-box 37, Folders 4-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 85603-85619.
    - Lightsource, binder 1, 1991 (Flat-box 37, Folders 6-11)
      Negatives: rolls: 9504, 9508-9517, 9532-9534, 66556-66562, 66841-66846, 66886-66893, 67156 68158-67163, 67486-67495, 71326-71329.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 9417-9419, 9447.
    - Lightsource, binder 2, 1991 (Flat-box 37, Folders 12-19)
      Negatives: rolls: 9351-9369, 9381-9396, 9417-9419, 9423-9450, 9473-9476, 9491-9493, 9495-9499, 75520.
    - Linc Quantum Analytics (6 folders), 1995 (Box-folder 37-20, Box-folder 38-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 63459-63483, 70934-70946, 70965-70974.
    - Mac Week, editorial, 1991 (Flat-box 38, Folders 6-11)
      Negatives: rolls: 69070-69081, 69083-69103, 69105-69107, 69403, 69404, 69406, 70412-70422.
    - Mac Week Anniversary, editorial, 1994 (Flat-box 38, Folders 12-16)
      Negatives: rolls: 76186-76193, 76329-76345.
    - Mac Week, editorial, 1995 (Flat-box 38, Folder 17)
      Negatives: rolls: 61238-61247.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 69082.
    - Mac World Anniversary, editorial (6 folders), 1993 (Box-folder 38-15, Box-folder 39-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 85041-85053, 85361-85369, 0800-0814, 75974-75979.
    - Mac World, 1994 (Flat-box 39, Folders 6-9)
      Negatives: rolls: 22436-22448, 92308-92323.
    - Misc. Tech, CKS, Lucent (Flat-box 39, Folder 10)
      Negatives: rolls: 78470-78474 (CKS), 41919 (Lucent).
    - Mitchell Hutchins, 1994 (Flat-box 39, Folders 11-16)
      Negatives: rolls: 503-532, 535-565.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 566.
    - NetFrame, 1993 (Flat-box 39, Folders 17-18)
      Negatives: rolls: 66382-66392, 68470-68472, 66449, 66450.
    - NetFrame, 1994-1995 (Flat-box 39, Folders 19-20)
      Negatives: rolls: 98489-98498, 103733-103745.
    - NetFrame, 1996 (Flat-box 40, Folders 1-2)
      Negatives: rolls: 01122-01137.
    - NetObjects, 1996 (Flat-box 40, Folders 3-6)
      Negatives: rolls: 0049, 0051, 0052, 0055, 0057, 0059, 0061, 0063, 0065, 0066, 0068, 95981-95983, 00275-00281, 00314-00319, 08141-08146, 00999-01007.
    - NetObjects, 1996 April (Flat-box 49, Folders 5-10)
      Negatives: rolls: 01613-01624, 01725-1736, 2077-2082, 02132, 01960-01968.
    - NetObjects, 1997 (Flat-box 40, Folders 7-8)
      Negatives: rolls: 23180-23193.
    - NetObjects employees, 1998 (Flat-box 40, Folders 9-11)
      Negatives: rolls: 42802-42824.
    - NetObjects, 1999 (Flat-box 40, Folders 12-15)
      Negatives: rolls: 69205-69232.
    - Netscape ReVerb, 1997 (Flat-box 40, Folders 16-19)
      Negatives: rolls: 21840-21869, 22981-22984.
    - Pixar (3 folders), 1996 (Box-folder 40-20, Box-folder 41-2)
      Negatives: rolls: 00954-00961, 00963-00971, 07835-07837, 07839-07841, 07843.
    - Planet Project, 2001 (Flat-box 41, Folders 3-4)
      Negatives: rolls: 64497-64511.
    - QVC, 1994 (Flat-box 41, Folders 5-20)
      Negatives: rolls: 76620, 76621, 76641-76652, 75959-75965, 45684-45689, 1176-1182, 1191-1199, 1083-1088, 1090-1096A, 77018-77053, 1108-1112, 1246-1253, 46402-46421, 46423, 1095-1107, 77133-77136, 77143-77152, 77154, 77155, 45508-45517, 45683.
    - QVC Network, 1994 (Flat-box 42, Folders 1-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 76951, 76955-76987, 79007-79010, 47005-47008, 1255.
    - Robert Stephens Broom & Broom, 1996 (Flat-box 42, Folders 6-9)
      Negatives: rolls: 00132-00151, 00621, 00622, 00624-00632.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls: 014, 45378, 45380, unlabeled.
    - Robert Stephens Trinet, 1995 (Flat-box 42, Folders 10-17)
      Negatives: rolls: 10131-10151, 10064-10080, 001-015, 45375-45380, 45594, unlabeled.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 10152-10165. There are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 45380, unlabeled.
    - Saffo, 1991 (Flat-box 42, Folders 18-19)
      Negatives: rolls: 9253-9267.
    - Sapient, binder 1 (6 folders), 2000 (Box-folder 42-20, Box-folder 43-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 214380-21468, 21513-21549.
    - Sapient, binder 2, "A Day in the Life,", 2000 (Flat-box 43, Folders 6-8)
      Negatives: rolls: 66601-66622, 66658-66665.
    - Sapient, binder 3, 2000 (Flat-box 43, Folders 9-13)
      Negatives: rolls: 66965- 67009.
    - SGI, 1996 (Flat-box 43, Folders 14-15)
      Negatives: rolls: 44712-44729, E1, E2.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 1, 1996 (Flat-box 43, Folders 16-18)
      Negatives: rolls: 08005-08014, 91751-91755, 91976, 96261, 96262, 1050-1056.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 2 (2 folders), 1996 (Box-folder 43-19, Box-folder 44-1)
      Negatives: rolls: 12362-12389.
    - Shoreline Pacific, Bielenberg Design, 1997 (Flat-box 44, Folder 2)
      Negatives: rolls: 16281-16289.
    - Shoreline Pacific, Brochure, binder 1, 1998 (Flat-box 44, Folders 3-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 1-7. 42091-42105, 42127, 42128.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 47816, 47818, 47827.
    - Shoreline Pacific, binder 2, 1998 (Flat-box 44, Folders 6-7)
      Negatives: rolls: 47815-47829.
      Note: there are no contact sheets for the following rolls: 47816, 47818, 47826, 47827.
    - Strategic Pacific, binder 4, 1994 (Flat-box 44, Folders 8-13)
      Negatives: rolls: 76774-76785, 76787, 76788 76800, 76801, 79292-79300, 79302, 79303, 79370-79374, 79376, 79377, 74149, 21390-21400, 91684-91690.
    - Strategic Pacific, 1995 (Flat-box 44, Folder 14)
      Negatives: rolls: 100725-100729.
    - Sun Microsystems, binder 1 (2 folders), 1992 (Box-folder 44-15, Box-folder 45-1)
      Negatives: rolls: 88192-88220, 88228, 88229, 88237, 88244, 88245, 88247-88249, 88259, 88267, 88272. 88285, 88288, 88292, 88294, 88301, 88311, 88312, 88322-88326, 88328, 88329, 88336, 88343, 88359, 88365, 88367, 88386, 88388-88394.
    - SVN, 1999 (Flat-box 45, Folders 2-6)
      Negatives: rolls: 9299-9317, 9322-9348.
      Note: there are no negatives for roll 9377.
    - Taligent, 1994 (Flat-box 45, Folders 7-12)
      Negatives: rolls: 76576-76589, 76649, 46678-46704, 78424-78437, 78484-78488.
    - TED III, binder 1 (8 folders), 1992 (Flat-box 45-13, Folder 46-7)
      Negatives: rolls: 1-12, 14-38, 40-97, 99, 100, 102-157, 190-192.
      Note: there are no negatives for rolls 13, 39, 101, 190.
    - Teseract, binder 1, 1994-1995 (Flat-box 46, Folders 8-12)
      Negatives: rolls: 94077-94111, 95423-95440.
    - Teseract, binder 2, 1994-1995 (Flat-box 46, Folders 13-16)
      Negatives: rolls: 96795-96802, 71412-71418, 71420-71422, 88005-88012, 99984-99990, 103097-103106.
    - Teseract, binder 3, 1994-1995 (Flat-box 46, Folders 17-20)
      Negatives: rolls: 89866-89872, 90205, 90206, 100259-100275, 103534-103538, 103540-103543.
    - TFI, 1987 (Flat-box 47, Folders 1-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 01120, 01121, 074650-074656, 08880, 13148, 13149, 18809-18811, 188650, 23695-23698, 17704, 17902, 17903,17905-17907, 30190, 30191, 31385, 25692-25696, 061299.
    - TFI, 1988 (Flat-box 47, Folders 4-13)
      Negatives: rolls: 05351-05356, 09550, 22200-22203, 22205-22208, 07323, 01201-01206, 061227, 061228, 061230, 061231,18190-18194, 31368, 31369-31384, 16300-16309, 18101, 18102, 18104, 15490-15495, 30484, 08331-08335, 08337-08340, 08346, 08347, 10358-10364, 74657.
    - TFI, binder 1, 1990 (Flat-box 48, Folders 6-10)
      Negatives: rolls: 8132, 8133, 8136-8139, 8238-8240, 8244-8251, 8302-8306, 37074-37081, 8352, 8353, 8364-8369, 4667, 8386-8391.
    - TFI, binder 2, 1990 (Flat-box 48, Folders 11-16)
      Negatives: rolls: 4666, 4668, 8404-8406. 8408-8413, 8425-8427, 8487-8489, 8506, 8507, 8609-8617, 8646-8661, 8663, 8729-8734.
    - TFI, binder 3 (6 folders), 1989 (Box-folder 47-14, Box-folder 48-5)
      Negatives: rolls: 11292, 11293, 11737-11739, 11793, 11795-11798, 15573, 16336-16339, 18409-18411, 188649, 22347-22350, 23155-23157, 24069-24071, 24073, 24074, 26942, 28979-28981, 27368, 28982-28984, 30147, 30484-30486, 30692-30696, 27-34, 8038-8049, 8053-8064, 8131, 8135.
    - Trimble, 1995 (Flat-box 48, Folder 17)
      Negatives: rolls: 235-239.
    - United Technologies, 1995 (Flat-box 48, Folders 18-20)
      Negatives: rolls: 58013-58015, 58017-58034, 58098, 423.
    - Voyager, 1991 (Flat-box 49, Folders 1-3)
      Negatives: rolls: 6912-6915, 6917-6928, 6930-6933, 73898-73901.
    - Wollongong, 1995 (Flat-box 49, Folder 4)
      Negatives: rolls: 103721-103732.
  - Subseries 4. Tear Sheets
    Subseries 4. Tear Sheets consists of 2 folders of tear sheets relating to commercial photography jobs.
    - Doug Menuez tear sheets (Flat-box 79, Folders 1-2)
- Series 6. Accession 2008-118, 1.0 Linear feet
  This Series contains contact sheets and negatives relating to Go Corp. and Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen.
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    This subseries contains contact sheets relating to Go Corp. and Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen. Corresponding negatives are in Series 6, Subseries 3. Negatives (CLOSED to researchers) unless otherwise noted.
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Contact sheets: 9207-9208, 9212-9220
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Contact sheets: 9221-9232
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Contact sheets: 9233-9239, 64189-64194
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Contact sheets: 64195-64205
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Contact sheets: 64206-64213
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Contact sheets: 97729, 97743-97752 (no negatives for 97744)
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Contact sheets: 97753-97756, 02684-02690
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Contact sheets: 02691-02700
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 9)
      Contact sheets: 02701-02713
  - Subseries 2. Selects
    This subseries contains contact sheets relating to Go Corp. and Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, with specific frames marked for future digitization. Corresponding negatives are in Series 6, Subseries 3. Negatives (CLOSED to researchers) unless otherwise noted.
    - Go Corp. selects, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      Contact sheets: 9207-9208, 9213-9221, 9224, 9226-9227
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen selects, 1996 June (Box 1, Folder 11)
      Contact sheets: 97729, 97743, 97745, 97747-97751, 97753, 97754, 97756, 02684-02690, 02692-02694, 12694-12696, 12699-12700, 02701-02704, 02707-02708, 02710, 02713
  - Subseries 3. Negatives
    Series 6, Subseries 3. Negatives, is CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes. Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Subseries 1 and 2. To request copies of images, please refer to job and roll number.
    This subseries contains negatives corresponding to the contact sheets found in Series 6, Subseries 1 and 2.
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      Negatives: 9207-9208, 9212-9220
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      Negatives: 9221-9232
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      Negatives: 9233-9239, 64189-64194
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      Negatives: 64195-64205
    - Go Corp., 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Negatives: 64206-64213
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 6)
      Negatives: 97729, 97743, 97745-97752
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Negatives: 97753-97756, 02684-02690
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Negatives: 02691-02700
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Negatives: 02701-02713
    - Go Corp. selects, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      Negatives: 9207-9208, 9213-9221, 9224, 9226, 9227
    - Kleiner, Perkins, Caufield and Byers-Aspen selects, 1996 June (Box 2, Folder 11)
      Negatives: 97729, 97743, 97745, 97747-97751, 97753-97754, 97756, 02684-02690, 02692-02694, 12694-12696, 12699-12700, 02701-02704, 02707-02708, 02710, 02713
- Series 7. Accession 2008-179, 52.0 Linear feet
  Series 7. Accession 2008-179 is arranged into 4 subseries: Jobs, Portfolio, Publications and Tear Sheets and Prints. Subseries 1. Jobs consists of prints, contact sheets, transparencies, negatives and related material, such as caption sheets, model releases and correspondence, related to Menuez's photography jobs. Many of the photographs were commissioned for publication in Discover, USA Today, Time, Mac Week, Forbes, Fortune, US News and World Report, People, and others. Negatives have been separated and housed in flat boxes for preservation purposes, and are OPEN to researchers. Numbers of photographic materials by format are noted in scope and content notes of many folders, and are approximate. Subseries 2. Portfolio consists of a number of Menuez's professional portfolios and contains prints, negatives and slides. Subseries 3. Publications and Tear Sheets contains examples of Doug Menuez's photography in printed publications, including tear sheets, advertisements, magazines, annual reports, brochures, etc. Subseries 4. Prints contains prints related to Menuez's documentary photography jobs, photo shoots and photo essays.
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    This subseries consists of prints, contact sheets, transparencies, negatives and related material, such as caption sheets, model releases and correspondence, related to Menuez's photography jobs. Many of the photographs were commissioned for publication in Discover, USA Today, Time, Mac Week, Forbes, Fortune, US News and World Report, People, and others. Negatives have been separated and housed in flat boxes for preservation purposes, and are OPEN to researchers. Numbers of photographic materials by format are noted in scope and content notes of many folders, and are approximate.
    - Acer (Box 1, Folder 1)
      146 color transparencies
    - Acer - Annual Report/Selects (Box 1, Folder 2)
      45 color transparencies
    - Acer group shot (Flat-box 38, Folder 1)
      color negatives: 5 unnumbered rolls
    - Acer (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 1-15, 17-19 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Acer (1 of 2) (Flat-box 38, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 1-19
    - Acer (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 24725-24735 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Acer (2 of 2) (Flat-box 38, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 24725-24735
    - Acer - misc. slides (1 of 3), 1989 April (Box 1, Folder 5)
      214 color transparencies, sheets 1-12
    - Acer - misc. slides (2 of 3), 1989 April (Box 1, Folder 6)
      186 color transparencies, sheets 13-22
    - Acer - misc. slides (3 of 3), 1989 April (Box 1, Folder 7)
      111 color transparencies, sheets 23-28
    - Acer, 1989 April 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      color transparencies: 7 sheets
    - Acer, 1989 April 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Acer, 1989 April 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Acer, 1989 April 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Acer, 1989 April 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      color transparencies: 8 sheets